One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The clouds floating in the cobalt blue,
got lost and will soak us all tomorrow.
It'll be fine if you just smile before the sunset.
If it's your wish, you can just
say a spell in your chest.
For your hopes...
Our quick premonition
is showing in the rainbow colored music notes.
Won't you come with me?
We're fallen angels,
we'll fire arrows into your dreams.
What color shall we add
into the cobalt blue?
Destroy the sad reality that reflects in your eyes.
Let's raise our wings, full of warmth.
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts.
Two Days After the Incident.
The Strongest Family Lineage?!
The Vice-Admiral and The Revolutionary!
Water 7, Blue Station, Blue Station...
Please make sure you have all your belongings.
Forget the money. Just take it with you!
This sucks...
But man... this year's Aqua Laguna was powerful.
It doesn't seem like we'll be able to repair this ourselves...
T-That's...
Paulie from Dock 1.
What's he doing here in the back streets?
Paulie-san!
Move! Get outta here, you're in the way!
I'll leave this area to you, Dock 3.
Alright!
Dock 5, you take the area starting from the house next to the old rail line.
Yeah!
We still have our jobs to do, so I want this town fully repaired in one month!
At any rate!
Got it!
Amazing! They're so dependable.
That's the Galley-La Company for you!
North Coast: Franky House Ruins.
Whew... rebuilding just seems harder and harder.
Cause we're used to breaking things down right?
Camping again huh?
All right.
Sodom, and you too Gomorah,
You guys rest up for now.
The Reindeer said that Gomorah's eyesight should return if he lets them rest.
Really? That's great.
The Shipyard: Dock 1.
Let us meet the Pirates!
We want to apologize for accusing them of the assassination!
No way, the Pirates aren't meeting anyone.
At least let us thank whoever it was who saved Iceberg-san's life!
Water 7 News! Can we get a comment from the heroes who saved the mayor?
Give it up, it's impossible right now.
Then a picture at least!
I told you no!
If you need a replacement secretary for Kalifa, let me do it!
I'll help with anything!
Amazing! What inhuman strength!
Is this alright?
Yeah, thank you!
What else would you expect from a giant?!
If it's stuff like this then ask us anytime!
Oh yea, Sniper King?
Are you alright here?
If our bosses' fight isn't over, then there's no way we can go to that island.
We'll help this island out a bit, and then take our time and return to Elbaf.
If you want to, we'll take you along with us.
I...
Galley-La Company's Main Office.
The Remains of Iceberg's House.
Temporary Headquarters.
I see, so you burned the blueprints...
It's for the best.
You've gained the World Government's resentment as well.
Yeah, I guess.
So, what have you been drawing all this time?
This time when Aqua Laguna came...
The ground was quaking with anxiety...
That the day when this entire island will be swallowed into the sea is nearby.
So, what'll you do?
I'm going to make this island float on the sea.
What!? Make Water Seven... a ship?!
C-Can that even be done?!
Did you forget?
The back of the man who could make the impossible possible.
We were always watching him.
If you're a man...
Do it with a "Don".
That's how he was.
Hello?
Oh, is that you, Brother?
Let me tell you. It finally came. We're where it arrived off the sea train.
Your 200 million beli item.
It's finally here...
Temporary Headquarters.
Special Pirates' Room,
Including Kitchen, Bath and Toilet.
I'm comin' in guys.
Granny Kokoro!
Yo, comin' in!
And you guys too.
You, just wait outside.
It seems you all finally woke up.
To sleep for two days, you must have been really worn out.
I guess that's expected.
Oh, the Pirate King sure seems to be feeling good.
Oh? You're mistaken.
About what?
After the fight he collapsed, but he was still dying to eat.
He seems to have invented a technique to eat while sleeping.
He's sleeping?!
Amazing, Pirate bro!
He's a pretty skilled guy.
Oh yea, the Log Pose should be set again after 2 or 3 days!
What happened here?!
Even if the Log is set, we can't move forward anymore...
The 100 Million beli we worked so hard for to buy us a new ship...
Our clothes... our furniture... Bellemere-san's orange trees... all of it...
Aqua Laguna carried it all away...
We can't go anywhere anymore...
We left all of it at the inn in the back streets.
Oh, so that's what the visitors out front are for.
Visitors?
My Orange Trees!
I thought they'd never come back!
Thank goodness!
Actually, while we thought you were responsible for Iceburg's assassination,
Your stuff crossed our minds, so we seized it all.
Sorry about that.
It's alright! Thank you!
Well, that's good.
Hey, we're coming in.
We're back.
Oh, Chopper.
And Robin-chwan~!
That was heavy wasn't it? Now please, right this way...
Thank you.
I went and checked on the Franky Family's wounds,
and I didn't let Robin out of my sight!
Good work!
I already told you I'm not going anywhere.
You promise?
I promise.
Look you two, my orange trees were okay.
All our money and stuff is back!
Really?
Now we can continue our voyage!
Yay! That's great!
Feeling super you guys?! Everybody...
Not everybody is around... Well, whatever...
Franky, what are you up to all of a sudden?
Listen!
I have something important to tell you.
There's an island, constantly at war...
What's this out of nowhere?
You just come in and start talking, if it's not an apology then we're not listening.
Shut up! Be quiet and listen.
Since the war started, if a person were to try living on that island under that rain of shells.
The people would die, the town would die. They'd be cremated with their ruins.
There was something still standing, a sturdy tree.
No matter what happened, it wouldn't fall.
People gathered near the tree and built a city... and a country.
There are only a few in the world.
The name of that strongest tree is...
The Treasure Wood Adam.
A tree?
A tree? What about it?
In our routes, having even a piece of that tree show up is extremely rare.
I wanted it but...
It's an item that costs 200 million.
I couldn't get my hands on it.
And what appeared before me but a group of pirates carrying a ton of money, you guys.
Why you! You used our money to buy something like that, didn't you?!
Just let me finish!
A long time ago, I decided I would never build a ship again.
But before long, to catch up to a man I admired, and to reach my own goal,
I drew up the blueprints for a ship...
My dream is to use that treasure wood and just one last time...
Make a ship, able to sail any sea. I'm going to make a Dream Ship.
I already have the wood, and the blueprints. With this I can make it.
So, when it's done...
Would you all sail in the ship I created?!
Then...?
So, you mean you'll give us that ship!?
Yeah.
If people who I like are sailing it.
That's what will make me happiest.
It's something I was only able to make because of your "investment" after all.
The only ship that ever sailed around the world,
Gold Roger's Oro Jackson, was made from this wood.
I'll definitely...
Show you an amazing ship.
Can't be helped, you and Tom-san are the same after all.
Just like a carpenter...
That's true, now...
Now I can understand how Tom-san felt when he died with his pride.
You're really a good guy! We'll take it! Thank you Franky!
Onto the next island!
This is great! Luffy! We've got a ship!
This is bad, we were found out this quickly, and Luffy's still sleeping!
I have to let them know fast!
What?!
It's them... they're here to capture the pirates.
Even though they're the heroes who saved Iceburg's life.
Hey, look over there!
That's Vice-Admiral Garp's warship from Headquarters.
Did you say Garp?
Isn't he the legendary marine who cornered Gold Roger countless times?
Why is such an amazing marine...
This is bad for the pirates.
The... sea?
Crap, was it the other direction?
W-Wait a second officers. There's no one but our president back-
Stop blathering! There should be pirates back here.
We said there aren't!
W-Wait you can't!
Wait, over there the Straw Ha-
Idiot!
You two, wait here.
Yessir!
What the...?
Who is it?
Are you the Straw Hat Pirates?
There're some men here who want to meet Monkey D. Luffy.
The Navy?!
Wake up!
Luffy!
It hurts! It hurts!
"It hurts"? What are you saying? That was a punch. For it to hurt a rubber man-
There's no defense against a fist of love.
I heard you've been acting pretty recklessly...
Luffy.
G- G- G-
Grandpa?!
Now Luffy,
Don't you think you owe me an apology?
Marine HQ Vice Admiral
Monkey D. Garp
"Garp The Fist"
Garp... isn't that the name of that marine hero!?
Luffy, is your grandpa really...?
He is, don't try fighting him.
I was almost killed by grandpa tons of times in the past.
Come on now, don't start speaking ill of me.
When I tossed you into that bottomless ravine,
And left you alone in the jungle at night,
And tied you to balloons and sent you flying into the sky,
All of it was to make you into a strong man!
I think I've just seen part of what gave Luffy his endless will to live...
In the end I left you with a close friend to continue your training with Ace.
And while you were out of my sight this has happened...
I did all that to forge you into a strong marine!!!
I always told you that I wanted to be a pirate didn't I!?
You were corrupted by that "Red Hair"!
It's nonsense!
I- I owe my life to Shanks!
Don't insult him!
Do you mean to tell your own Grandpa what to do?!
I'm sorry!
Emergency! Luffy was caught by the Navy!
Luffy!
This is bad, if we try to fight they'll jump right on top of us!
They fell asleep?!
So, what do we do now?
I've never been in a situation like this!
Uh oh, I fell asleep...
Wake up Luffy!
Is that how you act towards someone scolding you?!
First of all, where do you get off speaking like that to your grandpa?!
Oh whatever, just do what you want...
So Luffy's Grandpa is a Headquarters Marine?!
This is getting crazy.
I-I-It huuuuurts...
Do you even know what level of Pirate that "Red Hair" you keep going on about is!?
Shanks? And the guys?
Are Shanks and everybody doing alright? Where are they!?
Whether they're fine or not...
With as many pirates out there now as there are stars,
Like Whitebeard, he is one of the four great pirates!
Those who rule over the latter half of the Grand Line as if they were emperors.
We call them the Four Emperors!
In order to reign in these four men, Marine HQ and the Seven Warlords of the Sea were assembled.
These three great powers form a delicate balance that keeps peace around the world from crumbling.
I don't really get it, but if he's fine then okay.
Man, this brings back memories...
What is his connection with Red Hair?
Luffy said that he asked him to take care of that straw hat for him.
I didn't know he was such an amazing person.
It's over here, Zoro-san!
Damn, the marines are already here!
Please go on ahead.
We're really...
We're really sorry we tried to mug you!
Don't worry about it. Thanks for showing me the way.
Later.
Oh? What is going on?
It's the bounty head, the pirate hunter Zoro.
Oh? Luffy's crewmate right?
He seems to be pretty tough.
Heh, you two, try and stop him!
Yessir!
Kukuri knives huh? You're using something pretty unusual.
Oh, Zoro wait! There's no reason to fi-
What the...! Why you!
Shave!
That technique...
Sergeant Major!
Sergeant!
Really, you're no match at all.
You're as strong as I thought. Just what I'd expect.
I've lost.
Luffy-san, Zoro-san.
It's been a while.
Do you know who I am?
Who?
It's me, Coby!
Don't you remember?
Coby?
Coby?!
Coby is my friend but... but the Coby I knew was a lot smaller.
I'm that Coby!
That same cry-baby good-for-nothing Coby.
Are you serious?!
That Coby... why is he on the Grand Line?
I'm still not used to being a commissioned officer but,
When I heard the two of you were nearby, I couldn't resist coming to see you.
It's because of you two that we've become who we are!
Marine HQ Sergeant Major
Coby
Marine HQ Sergeant
Helmeppo
Well, I'll give you that much.
A lot has happened... right now we're being trained by Vice Admiral Garp at headquarters.
So that's what happened?
But man, there's a limit to how fast you should grow up, you surprised me.
You were a bit rounder back then too.
You must be pretty tired after the incident, sorry to disturb you.
It's fine. It's been a while, so let's make it a party!
Wait a second! You guys!
You didn't recognize me at all did you?!
Who're you?
It's me! M-E!
No idea, who are you?
The answer is...
Helmeppo.
Captain Morgan's son, Helmeppo.
I'm the man who almost drove you to the death penalty, Roronoa Zoro!
Really now, stop joking around.
We can't have you bullying people now.
You seem cheerful for a corpse, Roronoa Zoro.
Stop!
I'm that idiot who rode on his father's fame!
Oh? That was you?
Hey!
Oh yeah, there was a guy like that... that was you?
I knew it... I still can't forgive these guys, Coby!
It can't be avoided Helmeppo-san, you can't dodge your past.
That was it?
That was it.
Now then, you guys.
Sir!
Fix this wall.
But you did that yourself...
If you want us to fix it, then why did you even break it?
Entering that way is cooler.
Please don't break things for a reason like that!
Fine, if you want us to fix it, then you need to help too.
Alright.
Your grandpa is pretty famous isn't he?
I guess, I don't know much about what he does though.
By the way Luffy, I heard you met your old man.
Huh? Dad?
What do you mean by dad?
Do I have a dad?
What's that? So he didn't introduce himself then?
I heard he saw you off at Loguetown!
Luffy's father was in that town?
What is my dad like?
I wonder what Luffy's father is like...
The name of your father is...
Monkey D. Dragon.
He's a revolutionary.
Dragon?
The revolutionary Dragon had a son!?
Luffy-san is that Dragon's kid...
That means... that Dragon is Vice-Admiral Garp's kid...
What the hell is up with this family?
This is the first time I've heard Dragon's full name!
Hey guys, why is everyone so...
Idiot! You don't know who Dragon is!?
Your father is a completely outrageous man!
Hey, Robin...
How should I explain this...
Pirates wouldn't usually try by themselves to disrupt the government or marines...
But there is currently a power that is trying to directly oppose the World Government.
That would be the Revolutionary Army. And the man at it's center would be Dragon.
Right now throughout the world this ideology is being spread.
Encouraging countries to overthrow their monarchies.
Countless countries have already fallen.
As expected, the World Government was upset,
And has labeled the puppet master Dragon the most dangerous criminal in the world,
They have been constantly pursuing him but...
They couldn't find even a trace of where he had come from.
He was a mysterious man...
And yet...
And yet...?
I probably shouldn't have said all that.
So...
Forget all that!
Translation, skywalker6705 @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Initial timing, Kuzan @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Quality checking, Sewil
Editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, MaideV and Halee
Raw providing, SOFCJ-Raws